Problem statement : get the data provided in stdin and store it in a file.

Here, i have read the input in blocks. Fixed buffer length has been initialized to 1024. 
So when we give the data via stdin, the program reads first n characters, say 1024 and store 
it in a file and read the next 1024 characters and store it in the file and 
the process continues till the program detects EOF signal.


The data is stored as a binary to support unicode characters.
Each write operation is checked if it is successful. If not then probably the user doesnt have enough space to write the data and the program ends.
During the first write operation, the file is created and the data is dumped into the file. From the next write operation, the data will 
just gets appended int the same file.